=My Sweet Professor= =Episode 9=
= أستاذي الحلو = = الحلقة 9 =
Ah.
آه.
Crap.
حماقة.
I forgot.
انا نسيت.
Huo Shang, where's my car?
هوه شانغ ، أين سيارتي؟
Was it towed away by the traffic police?
هل تم جرها من قبل شرطة المرور؟
Every time I run into you, nothing good happens.
في كل مرة أواجهك ، لا يحدث شيء جيد.
You should stay away from me.
يجب أن تبتعد عني.
What? You didn't tow my car away?
ماذا؟  أنت لم تسحب سيارتي بعيدًا؟
They don't have your car?
ليس لديهم سيارتك؟
Hey.
يا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
To say sorry to you,
لأقول آسف لك ،
I promise
أعدك
before you get off work,
قبل أن تغادر العمل ،
you will find your car in the parking lot of the hospital
ستجد سيارتك في موقف السيارات بالمستشفى
safe and sound.
السلامة والعافية.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Go.
يذهب.
Hey, riche.
مهلا ، الثراء.
Let's be friends.
لنكن أصدقاء.
Ah.
آه.
My limbs are weak
أطرافي ضعيفة
and I've been feeling
وكنت أشعر
dizzy and tired these days.
بالدوار والتعب هذه الأيام.
But I've still got piles of work to do.
لكن لا يزال لدي أكوام من العمل لأقوم به.
Well...
نحن سوف...
I'll do them for you.
سأفعلها من أجلك.
Let me check your pulse.
دعني أتحقق من نبضك.
Did dizziness,
هل الدوخة ،
nausea, and loss of appetite
الغثيان وفقدان الشهية
happened to you?
حصل لك؟
They did.
لقد فعلوا.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
Congrats.
تهاني.
You're pregnant.
انت حامل.
He's pregnant.
إنه حامل.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Go.
يذهب.
Get to work.
اذهب للعمل.
(Linquan First Hospital)
(مستشفى Linquan الأول)
(To: Dr. Gao, Gao Yuan)
(إلى: د.جاو ، جاو يوان)
(Huo Shang: How do you like your new car?)
(هوه شانغ: كيف تحب سيارتك الجديدة؟)
Dr. Gao must be thrilled.
لابد أن الدكتور جاو يشعر بسعادة غامرة.
You didn't see it.
لم تره.
I decorated the car perfectly.
لقد زينت السيارة بشكل مثالي.
(Gao Yuan) I'm sure it shows your good taste.
(جاو يوان) أنا متأكد من أنه يظهر ذوقك الجيد.
Hey.
يا.
Huo Shang!
هوه شانغ!
I need you to give me back my car right now!
أريدك أن تعيد لي سيارتي الآن!
He yelled at you?
صرخ فيك؟
Don't worry, Mr. Huo.
لا تقلق ، سيد هوو.
I have a better way.
لدي طريقة أفضل.
Hey.
يا.
I'll give you a ride.
سأوصلك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
The subway station isn't far.
محطة مترو الأنفاق ليست بعيدة.
Eh.
إيه.
Mr. Huo.
السيد هوو.
What do you want exactly?
ماذا تريد بالضبط؟
I still have to go to work.
لا يزال يتعين علي الذهاب إلى العمل.
Get in the car.
اركب السيارة.
Isn't it cozier than the subway?
أليس أكثر دفئًا من مترو الأنفاق؟
If you didn't take away my car,
إذا لم تأخذ سيارتي ،
I wouldn't need to take the subway.
لن أحتاج إلى ركوب مترو الأنفاق.
But you didn't accept the new car.
لكنك لم تقبل السيارة الجديدة.
Come on, Huo Shang,
تعال ، هوه شانغ ،
you weren't like this before.
لم تكن هكذا من قبل.
How did you become like this?
كيف صرت هكذا؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
What am I like now?
ما الذي يعجبني الآن؟
You're like a nouveau riche.
أنت مثل الأثرياء الجدد.
Nouveau riche?
غني جديد؟
Do I look like that?
هل أبدو هكذا؟
I'm the CEO.
أنا الرئيس التنفيذي.
Hey.
يا.
Drive slowly.
قد ببطء.
Eyes on the road.
عيون على الطريق.
Alright. Relax.
على ما يرام.  الاسترخاء.
Gao Yuan.
جاو يوان.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
=My Sweet Professor=
= أستاذي الحلو =